export const QuizzQuestins = [
    {
        category: "Entertainment Video Games",
        type: "multiple",
        difficulty: "hard",
        question: "What does HTML stand for?",
        correct_answer: "Home Text Markup Language",
        answers: [
            " Hyperlinks and Text Markup Language",
            " Home Tool Markup Language",
            " Hyper Text Markup Language",
            "Home Text Markup Language",
        ]
    },
    {
        category: "Animals",
        type: "multiple",
        difficulty: "easy",
        question: "Which of the following tag can be used to associate a caption together with some embedded content in HTML5?",
        correct_answer: "figure",
        answers: [
            "footer",
            "nav",
            "dialog",
            "figure",
        ]
    },
    {
        category: "Entertainment Books",
        type: "multiple",
        difficulty: "hard",
        question: "Which of the following tag automatically focus one particular form field in HTML5?",
        correct_answer: "autofocus",
        answers: [
            "output",
            "placeholder",
            "autofocus",
            "required",
        ]
    },
    {
        category: "Entertainment Comics",
        type: "multiple",
        difficulty: "easy",
        question: " Which of the following attribute triggers an abort event?",
        correct_answer: "onabort",
        answers: [
            "offline",
            "onabort",
            "abort",
            "onbeforeonload",
        ]
    },
    {
        category: "Entertainment Board Games",
        type: "multiple",
        difficulty: "medium",
        question: "Which of the following attribute triggers event before the document is printed?",
        correct_answer: "onbeforeprint",
        answers: [
            "onbeforeprint",
            "onafterprint",
            "onprint",
            "beforeprint",
        ]
    },
    {
        category: "Geography",
        type: "multiple",
        difficulty: "easy",
        question: "Which of the following attribute triggers event when the browser starts to load the media data?",
        correct_answer: "onloadstart",
        answers: [
            "onloadstart",
            "onloadedmetadata",
            "onmessage",
            "onoffline",
        ]
    },
    {
        category: "History",
        type: "multiple",
        difficulty: "medium",
        question: "How many generic fonts are available?",
        correct_answer: "5",
        answers: [
            "2",
            "3",
            "5",
            "4",
        ]
    },
    {
        category: "Animals",
        type: "boolean",
        difficulty: "easy",
        question: "What tag will have the information that will appear in the title bar of the Web Page?",
        correct_answer: "Title Tag",
        answers: [
            "HTML Tag",
            "Body Tag",
            "Head Tag",
            "Title Tag",
        ]
    },
    {
        category: "General Knowledge",
        type: "multiple",
        difficulty: "medium",
        question: "What identifies the end of a two-sided tag?",
        correct_answer: "Closing Tag",
        answers: [
            "End Tag",
            "Closing Tag",
            "Last Tag",
            "Finish Tag",
        ]
    },
    {
        category: "History",
        type: "multiple",
        difficulty: "medium",
        question: "What tag will create a line break?",
        correct_answer: "Break tag",
        answers: [
            "Title tag",
            "List tag",
            "Break tag",
            "Body tag",
        ]
    },
    {
        category: "Entertainment Video Games",
        type: "multiple",
        difficulty: "hard",
        question: "What does the acronym HTML represent?",
        correct_answer: "Hypertext Markup Language",
        answers: [
            "Hypertext Markup Language",
            "Hyperlink Markup Language",
            "Hypertext Marks Language",
            "Hypertext",
        ]
    },
    {
        category: "Entertainment Video Games",
        type: "boolean",
        difficulty: "medium",
        question: "What tag usually contains information about the document that will not appear in the Web Page?",
        correct_answer: "Head Tag",
        answers: [
            "HTML Tag",
            "Body Tag",
            "Head Tag",
            "Title Tag",
        ]
    },
    {
        category: "Entertainment Japanese Anime %26 Manga",
        type: "multiple",
        difficulty: "medium",
        question: "What tag is used to insert a graphic?",
        correct_answer: "The image src tag",
        answers: [
            "The graphic tag",
            "The image src tag",
            "The image tag",
            "The graphic src tag",
        ]
    },
    {
        category: "Entertainment Video Games",
        type: "multiple",
        difficulty: "medium",
        question: "How many HTML headings are available?",
        correct_answer: "6",
        answers: [
            "2",
            "3",
            "4",
            "6",
        ]
    },
    {
        category: "History",
        type: "multiple",
        difficulty: "easy",
        question: "What tag will have the information that will be displayed in the Web Page?",
        correct_answer: "Body Tag",
        answers: [
            "HTML Tag",
            "Body Tag",
            "Head Tag",
            "Title Tag",
        ]
    },
    {
        category: "Entertainment Television",
        type: "multiple",
        difficulty: "hard",
        question: "What tag tells the computer that the document is going to be a HTML document?",
        correct_answer: "HTML Tag",
        answers: [
            "Tell Tag",
            "HTML Tag",
            "Creation Tag",
            "Identify Tag",
        ]
    },
    {
        category: "Entertainment Music",
        type: "multiple",
        difficulty: "medium",
        question: "What identifies the start of a two-sided tag?",
        correct_answer: "Opening Tag",
        answers: [
            "Start Tag",
            "Beginning Tag",
            "Opening Tag",
            "Number One Tag",
        ]
    },
    {
        category: "General Knowledge",
        type: "boolean",
        difficulty: "easy",
        question: "What tag will identify items that will be placed in a list?",
        correct_answer: "Buck",
        answers: [
            "The ol tag",
            "The ul tag",
            "The li tag",
            "The br tag",
        ]
    },
    {
        category: "Entertainment Video Games",
        type: "multiple",
        difficulty: "medium",
        question: "When using a color value, the numbers are separated by ______________?",
        correct_answer: "Commas",
        answers: [
            "Periods",
            "Commas",
            "Semi Colons",
            "Colons",
        ]
    },
    {
        category: "History",
        type: "multiple",
        difficulty: "hard",
        question: "If you were to display the following HTML code using a Browser, what would appear in the title bar of the Web Browser?",
        correct_answer: "HTML Assessment",
        answers: [
            "Nothing",
            "HTML Assessment",
            "This Assessment is on HTML Basics",
            "CSS",
        ]
    }
]